http://claylink.com/privacy

Holiday Clay Jam 2020Cup: The Intimate Object XVIFall Clay Jam 2020Summer is Served: PlatesThe Functional Canvas VExquisite Forms IIFong Choo - Eighteen GemsWoodfireworks IIIThe CollectionsThe Cup CollectionThe Bowl CollectionThe Plates & Platters CollectionThe Vase CollectionThe Pouring Vessels CollectionThe Lidded Vessel CollectionThe Cooking & Serving CollectionThe Sculpture CollectionRepresented Artists A-CSenta AcheeAraceli AdamsJamie AdamsKristine AguilarRachel AkinChris AlveshereCarragh AmosMary-Lydia AndersenMindy AndrewsMarion AngelicaLinda ArbuckleMark ArnoldJoAnn F AxfordNoel BaileyMarian BakerMariana BaqueroCindy BarnettRickie BarnettJamie Bates SloneBen BatesHayne BaylessCasey BeckMeghan BergmanNicholas BernardLesley BevanAshley BevingtonMarvin BjurlinSandra BlainBeth BolglaDavid BoltonCatherine BoswellEric BotbylEmilie Bouvet-BoisclairJoe BovaHelle BovbjergAriel BowmanMeredith BradleyAngel BrameNathan BrayMichael BridgesJessica BroadJake BrodskyAmy BrummondCate Brus-AustinAsta BublieneLaurie CafferyRebecca CampbellDawn CandyDanielle CarelockNathan CarnesErin CarpenterLaura CasasHeidi McKay CastoMichael ChappellAdam ChauHoyt ChildersIan ChildersFong ChooVictoria ChristenAdriana ChristiansonLinda ChristiansonBrandon ChristySam ChumleyMike CinelliCraig CliffordJeff ClineMichelle CoakesJenn ColeFaith ConnorMartha CookJulie CrosbyChristy CulpRepresented Artists D-FPriscilla DahlKari DarrSarah De BerryElise DelfieldHarris DellerJoseph DelphiaAndrea DennistonMarcel DeolazoGrace DePledgeNick DeVriesAvesha DeWolfeWill DickertMaria DonderoJustin DonofrioBarbara DonovanScott DooleyAudra DoughtyMary DrabikMichele DrossRuth EasterbrookAdrienne EliadesSarah Beth ElkinsCarole EppMachiko ErhardAllee EtheridgeMichelle EttrickAmy EvansAmanda FangueLauren FaustKatrina FekkesSusan FilleyTuile FionnualaAlexandra FitzGeraldHolly FrancisStephen D FrazierRepresented Artists G-KStuart GairStephanie GalliErnest GentryMike GesiakowskiDaniel GillbergJuana GneccoWendy GoldsmithCharlotte GordonRebecca A. GrantNancy GreenMel GriffinMike GriffinShirley GromenMartha H. GroverBrian GrowPauline GuideraChris GustinErik HaagensenDeborah HagerMichael Andrew HallAnnemiek HamelinkLisa HammondCasey HanrahanJulie HarbersMatthew HardwickDeborah HarrisStephen HawesEric HeerspinkMike HelkeElisa Helland-HansenKendall HerdelinAutumn HigginsSteven HillTiffany HiltonLynne HobaicaEric HoeferBarbara HoffmanSam HoffmanBettina HoldenErin HolmesNathan HoodNoelle HooverChris HosbachSamantha HostertZoey Murphy HouserIssac HowardTrista HudzikMaxine HugonHungryMunchyMatthew HyleckWalter HyleckMichelle ImAmy IrishMike JabburKirk JacksonAdam JennettDoug JeppesenGreta Michelle JoachimKyle JohnsAlex JohnsonFred JohnstonJordan JonesShikha JoshiDenise JoyalEmma Louise KayeBetsy KendrickDeirdre KerriganAshley KimKatherine KingdonMargaret KinkeadeJason KishellCarrie KitzkeJim KlingmanMadeline KlusmireLucien KoonceTim KowalczykKarin KraemerDavid Kenton KringDebbie KupinskyRepresented Artists L-NMartina LantinDick LehmanMorgan LevineKeok LimCarol LongRenee LoPrestiToni LoseySteve LoucksLouise LovelaceJessi MaddocksAnika MajorKatherine MaloneyMaureen MarcotteJuni MargrieRom MarinkovichJessie MartinAntonio MartinezTameria MartinezAnna MasciantonioClaire McCauleyLinda McFarlingSusan McHenryLesley McInallyAndrew McIntyreLorna MeadenEsther MechJacob MeerChristopher MeliaMelissa MenciniSam MendezMichelle MendlowitzBranan MercerCandice MetheRon MeyersBrooke MillecchiaPolina MillerReiko MiyagiNikki MizakRay MoralesSage MorganStephen MullinsKate Shakeshaft MurrayRyan MyersMark NafzigerKelsey NagyTed NealSamuel NewmanCJ NiehausSarah NikitopoulosNom CeramicsVanessa NorrisRepresented Artists O-RLindsay OesterritterLucy OgdenDebra OlivaAsa OlofssonLisa OrrMolly O'ShaughnessyMarsha OwenHolly OyadomariKatie PackElizabeth PaleyJess PalmerGillian ParkeDavid ParryNicole PaulinaBrandon PenaRichard PetersonRonan Kyle PetersonRon PhilbeckTeresa PietschSarah PikeSarah PiperJenny PopeClaire PrentonCarla PrinsterBrenda QuinnTyler QuintinFredi RahnJeremy RandallBeau RaymondDow RedcornTessa ReedNatalie Reed-GoehlDon ReynoldsMary RheinBarry RhodesAustin RiddleJoseph RinconesMonica RipleyTilla RodemannSusan Keller RodriguezCathy RoseAnn RuelLora RustRepresented Artists S-ZEileen SackmanAdrian SandstromMasa SasakiTed SaupePete ScherzerMatthew SchiemannRyan SchulzDeborah SchwartzkopfSam ScottLaurie Carretta ScuppGalen SedberryKen SedberryYoko Sekino-BoveNicole SerraLeland ShawTim ShermanHitomi ShibataTakuro ShibataJana ShimonovIsaac ShueAlison SmilesLiz SmithJohn SnyderHyojin SongNatalya SotsAmelia StampsChad SteveRebekah StricklandMike StumbrasWei SunKatie SuskoHeidi TarverCasey TaylorRobbie TeasdaleCharlie TefftAlexis TempletonSusan ThomasTiffany ThomasBritt ThorpAlex ThullenJohn TiltonJames TingeySue TirrellKyla ToomeySandra TorresMaliya Travers-CrumbLeilani TrinkaJack TroySara TrumanClovy Haruko TsuchiyaNala TurnerMomoko UsamiEric Van EimerenAna VarelaLynn Anne VerbeckDavid VollCarolyn Von ZabernMichael VorisekLansing WagnerGinny WatersMatthew WattersonAndrew and Katie WebsterMelissa WeissSherry WellsStephanie WilhelmBryan WilkersonIfe Marie WilliamsJoel WillsonBuilderburner CeramicsErik WilsonKari WoolseyDallas WootenMatthew WrenHedy YangMeghan YarnellLevi YastrowKarla YauchlerAshley YoungMonte YoungAnthony YoungChengOu YuLisa ZolandzCaleb Zouhary Advanced Search
About Us
Gallery Newsletter
Gallery Submissions
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Contact Us
Site Map
GALLERY CATALOG
Holiday Clay Jam 2020Cup: The Intimate Object XVI
My Account
Sign In
Create an Account
My Cart
item(s)
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for CharlieCummingsGallery.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 352-359-7172 or email charlie@charliecummingsgallery.com.
Home
Privacy Notice
Advanced Search
>Fall Clay Jam 2020Summer is Served: PlatesThe Functional Canvas VExquisite Forms IIFong Choo - Eighteen GemsWoodfireworks IIIThe CollectionsThe Cup CollectionThe Bowl CollectionThe Plates & Platters CollectionThe Vase CollectionThe Pouring Vessels CollectionThe Lidded Vessel CollectionThe Cooking & Serving CollectionThe Sculpture CollectionRepresented Artists A-CSenta AcheeAraceli AdamsJamie AdamsKristine AguilarRachel AkinChris AlveshereCarragh AmosMary-Lydia AndersenMindy AndrewsMarion AngelicaLinda ArbuckleMark ArnoldJoAnn F AxfordNoel BaileyMarian BakerMariana BaqueroCindy BarnettRickie BarnettJamie Bates SloneBen BatesHayne BaylessCasey BeckMeghan BergmanNicholas BernardLesley BevanAshley BevingtonMarvin BjurlinSandra BlainBeth BolglaDavid BoltonCatherine BoswellEric BotbylEmilie Bouvet-BoisclairJoe BovaHelle BovbjergAriel BowmanMeredith BradleyAngel BrameNathan BrayMichael BridgesJessica BroadJake BrodskyAmy BrummondCate Brus-AustinAsta BublieneLaurie CafferyRebecca CampbellDawn CandyDanielle CarelockNathan CarnesErin CarpenterLaura CasasHeidi McKay CastoMichael ChappellAdam ChauHoyt ChildersIan ChildersFong ChooVictoria ChristenAdriana ChristiansonLinda ChristiansonBrandon ChristySam ChumleyMike CinelliCraig CliffordJeff ClineMichelle CoakesJenn ColeFaith ConnorMartha CookJulie CrosbyChristy CulpRepresented Artists D-FPriscilla DahlKari DarrSarah De BerryElise DelfieldHarris DellerJoseph DelphiaAndrea DennistonMarcel DeolazoGrace DePledgeNick DeVriesAvesha DeWolfeWill DickertMaria DonderoJustin DonofrioBarbara DonovanScott DooleyAudra DoughtyMary DrabikMichele DrossRuth EasterbrookAdrienne EliadesSarah Beth ElkinsCarole EppMachiko ErhardAllee EtheridgeMichelle EttrickAmy EvansAmanda FangueLauren FaustKatrina FekkesSusan FilleyTuile FionnualaAlexandra FitzGeraldHolly FrancisStephen D FrazierRepresented Artists G-KStuart GairStephanie GalliErnest GentryMike GesiakowskiDaniel GillbergJuana GneccoWendy GoldsmithCharlotte GordonRebecca A. GrantNancy GreenMel GriffinMike GriffinShirley GromenMartha H. GroverBrian GrowPauline GuideraChris GustinErik HaagensenDeborah HagerMichael Andrew HallAnnemiek HamelinkLisa HammondCasey HanrahanJulie HarbersMatthew HardwickDeborah HarrisStephen HawesEric HeerspinkMike HelkeElisa Helland-HansenKendall HerdelinAutumn HigginsSteven HillTiffany HiltonLynne HobaicaEric HoeferBarbara HoffmanSam HoffmanBettina HoldenErin HolmesNathan HoodNoelle HooverChris HosbachSamantha HostertZoey Murphy HouserIssac HowardTrista HudzikMaxine HugonHungryMunchyMatthew HyleckWalter HyleckMichelle ImAmy IrishMike JabburKirk JacksonAdam JennettDoug JeppesenGreta Michelle JoachimKyle JohnsAlex JohnsonFred JohnstonJordan JonesShikha JoshiDenise JoyalEmma Louise KayeBetsy KendrickDeirdre KerriganAshley KimKatherine KingdonMargaret KinkeadeJason KishellCarrie KitzkeJim KlingmanMadeline KlusmireLucien KoonceTim KowalczykKarin KraemerDavid Kenton KringDebbie KupinskyRepresented Artists L-NMartina LantinDick LehmanMorgan LevineKeok LimCarol LongRenee LoPrestiToni LoseySteve LoucksLouise LovelaceJessi MaddocksAnika MajorKatherine MaloneyMaureen MarcotteJuni MargrieRom MarinkovichJessie MartinAntonio MartinezTameria MartinezAnna MasciantonioClaire McCauleyLinda McFarlingSusan McHenryLesley McInallyAndrew McIntyreLorna MeadenEsther MechJacob MeerChristopher MeliaMelissa MenciniSam MendezMichelle MendlowitzBranan MercerCandice MetheRon MeyersBrooke MillecchiaPolina MillerReiko MiyagiNikki MizakRay MoralesSage MorganStephen MullinsKate Shakeshaft MurrayRyan MyersMark NafzigerKelsey NagyTed NealSamuel NewmanCJ NiehausSarah NikitopoulosNom CeramicsVanessa NorrisRepresented Artists O-RLindsay OesterritterLucy OgdenDebra OlivaAsa OlofssonLisa OrrMolly O'ShaughnessyMarsha OwenHolly OyadomariKatie PackElizabeth PaleyJess PalmerGillian ParkeDavid ParryNicole PaulinaBrandon PenaRichard PetersonRonan Kyle PetersonRon PhilbeckTeresa PietschSarah PikeSarah PiperJenny PopeClaire PrentonCarla PrinsterBrenda QuinnTyler QuintinFredi RahnJeremy RandallBeau RaymondDow RedcornTessa ReedNatalie Reed-GoehlDon ReynoldsMary RheinBarry RhodesAustin RiddleJoseph RinconesMonica RipleyTilla RodemannSusan Keller RodriguezCathy RoseAnn RuelLora RustRepresented Artists S-ZEileen SackmanAdrian SandstromMasa SasakiTed SaupePete ScherzerMatthew SchiemannRyan SchulzDeborah SchwartzkopfSam ScottLaurie Carretta ScuppGalen SedberryKen SedberryYoko Sekino-BoveNicole SerraLeland ShawTim ShermanHitomi ShibataTakuro ShibataJana ShimonovIsaac ShueAlison SmilesLiz SmithJohn SnyderHyojin SongNatalya SotsAmelia StampsChad SteveRebekah StricklandMike StumbrasWei SunKatie SuskoHeidi TarverCasey TaylorRobbie TeasdaleCharlie TefftAlexis TempletonSusan ThomasTiffany ThomasBritt ThorpAlex ThullenJohn TiltonJames TingeySue TirrellKyla ToomeySandra TorresMaliya Travers-CrumbLeilani TrinkaJack TroySara TrumanClovy Haruko TsuchiyaNala TurnerMomoko UsamiEric Van EimerenAna VarelaLynn Anne VerbeckDavid VollCarolyn Von ZabernMichael VorisekLansing WagnerGinny WatersMatthew WattersonAndrew and Katie WebsterMelissa WeissSherry WellsStephanie WilhelmBryan WilkersonIfe Marie WilliamsJoel WillsonBuilderburner CeramicsErik WilsonKari WoolseyDallas WootenMatthew WrenHedy YangMeghan YarnellLevi YastrowKarla YauchlerAshley YoungMonte YoungAnthony YoungChengOu YuLisa ZolandzCaleb Zouhary
Gallery Information
About Us
Gallery Newsletter
Gallery Submissions
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Terms & Conditions
Contact Us
Please enter your email address below to create account.
Email
Sign In
To Top
